effectmatrix.com 2012-10-03

# EffectMatrix Ltd privacy

**Privacy**

EffectMatrix Software is committed to protecting your privacy. We will only collect your personal information for defined purposes. We do not distribute or share your personal information beyond what is strictly necessary to fulfill our obligations to you. We may share your information only with partners who adhere to EffectMatrix's commitment to protecting your privacy. EffectMatrix Software will not sell your personal information in any manner whatsoever. 

**What information do we collect? What do we use it for?**

When you place an order on our website, your full name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card number, and credit card expiration date will be required. The information is used to complete the transaction and help us provide better support and services to you.

**How do the 3rd party credit card processors protect customer's information?**

EffectMatrix software uses secure server hosted by PLIMUS that encrypt all the customer's personal information before it is sent to us, including name, address, credit card number, credit card expiration date, etc. Encryption works to prevent any malicious use of your personal information. Your credit card information is only used for online transition. 

**PLIMUS**

PLIMUS is an advanced secure online payment service for software registration . EffectMatrix Software uses PLIMUS to provide you with very secure and fast online purchase. 

About cookies 

In order to better understand what services are valuable to our customers, we use "cookies". A cookie is a small text file that a Website writes to your hard drive. Cookies let the web page server know that you have returned to this site. Cookies also can determine other information, such as the daily visitors to our website and the pages of the site most frequently visited. Cookies are unique and can only be read by the server that assigns them. They cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses. 

You can change the settings in your browser to prevent cookies if you do not want to have a cookie set when you visit our website
